- 跟他讲 跟他讲   - 跟他讲啦
- Tell him. Please tell him.     - Tell him.
- 闭嘴   - 跟我讲什么？
- Shut up.     - Tell me what?
- 你连看他都不敢   - 跟我说啦 拜托
- You won't even look at him.     - Oh, come on, tell me.
多一个理由解释为何女人都不看我 也不错
I could use another reason why women won't look at me.
好啦 好啦 好啦
All right, all right, all right.
昨晚 我梦到…
Last night, I had a dream...
你跟我…
...that, um, you and I were, uh...
在这张桌子上做
Doing it on this table.
- 喔   - 漂亮的梦中上垒
- Wow.     - Excellent dream score.
为什么…？你为什么会做那种梦？
Why...? Why would you dream that?
更重要的是 我厉害吗？
More importantly, was I any good?
嗯 真的很不错
Well, you were pretty damned good. Ha, ha.
有意思 因为在我的梦中 我笨拙到让人吃惊
Interesting, because in my dreams, I'm surprisingly inadequate.
昨晚你在这张桌子上非常熟练
Well, last night, you seemed to know your way around the table.
能够这样分享真好
I love it when we share.
你还好吧？
You okay there?
真不敢相信你们在她的梦里做爱
I can't believe you two had sex in her dream.
对不起 就那么一次而已
I'm sorry. It was a one-time thing.
我非常醉 而且那是别人的潜意识
I was very drunk, and it was someone else's subconscious.
- 嘿 瑞秋   - 嗯
- Hello, Rachel.     - Ugh.
下来
Get off.
拿来 你们想象得到让我操作钻床吗？
Ooh. Oh, give me. Can you see me operating a drill press?
不知道 你穿什么衣服？
I don't know. What are you wearing?
菲比 你为什么想操作钻床？
Pheebs, why would you want to operate a drill press?
短期打工
Just for some short-term work.
直到我的一些按摩客人回来
You know, till I get back some of my massage clients.
又是海盗吗？
Pirates again?
不是 完全无关
No. Nothing like that.
我只是个白痴
I'm just such a dummy.
我在一个 "在家自我按摩" 讲座教他们
I taught this "Massage Yourself at Home" workshop.
结果他们真的照做
And they are.
嘿 钱德 她可以去你那里工作
Hey, hey, Chan, she could work for you.
谢谢你 乔伊 那真是个好主意
Thanks, Joey. That's a good idea.
什么？我可以啊 真的 要做什么？
What? I could. I could do it. What is it?
我的秘书要请假
Well, my secretary's gonna be out.
她要做单边缩乳手术
She's having one of her boobs reduced.
一整个复杂的乳房故事
It's a whole big boob story.
当秘书我没问题
I could be a secretary.
嗯 难说 不知道你会不会喜欢…
Well, I don't know if it's your kind of thing...
因为一整天大部分的时间…
...because, uh, it involves a lot of being normal...
都要当个正常人
...ahem, for a large portion of the day.
我办得到
I could do that.
- 你在玩什么？ - 我的哔哔机
- What are you playing with?     - It's my new beeper.
搞什么？古生物学家需要什么哔哔机？
Why the hell does a paleontologist need a beeper for?
恐龙有紧急状况时用？
Is it, like, for dinosaur emergencies?
"救命 快来 他们仍然处于绝种状态"
"Help, come quick! They're still extinct!"
不是 卡萝准备要生产时用的 她什么时候都找得到我
No, it's for when Carol goes into labor. She can get me wherever I am.
她只需要打55JIMBO
All she has to do is dial 55-JIMBO.
好酷的号码 而且小孩也可以取这个名字
A cool phone number and a possible name for the kid.
- 我们晚点再见   - 要去跟小伊森约会了吗？
- I'll see you guys later.     - Off to see young Ethan?
谢谢你哦
Thank you.
小伊森是有多小？很小吗？
How young is young Ethan? Young?
我们的年龄
He's our age.
我们那时几岁…？
When we were?
- 好吧 他读大学四年级   - 大学？
- Okay, he's a senior in college.     - College?
- 喔   - 哇
- Ooh.     - Whoa.
这个大男孩不在乎你的年龄吗？
And this man-child has no problem with how old you are?
当然不在乎
No, of course not.
那根本不是问题…
It's not even an issue...
因为我跟他说我22岁
...because I told him I was 22.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What?     - What?
- 怎么 说我22岁没人相信吗？ - 25 26还有可能
- Oh, I can't pass for 22?     - Well, maybe 25, 26.
- 我26岁   - 看吧
- I am 26.     - There you go.
你听到了吗？
Can you hear that?
听到了
Yeah. Ha, ha.
你电话接起来 那声音就会停
That'll stop when you pick up the phone.
哦 哈哈
Oh. Ha, ha.
- 好 开始了   - 好吧
- Okay. Ooh, I'm on.     - Okay.
宾先生办公室
Mr. Bing's office.
不好意思 他现在正在开会
No, I'm sorry, he's in a meeting right now.
我哪有在开会 我人就在…
I'm not in a meeting. I'm right...
请问他知道这是有关哪一方面的事吗？
Will he know what this is in reference to?
他有你的电话号码吗？
And he has your number?
好 我一定会转达留言 再见
All right, I'll see that he gets the message. Bye-bye.
- 什么？ - 罗斯打来打招呼
- What?     - Ross says hi.
啊
Ah.
好好玩哦 好 现在我们要做什么？
This is so fun. All right, what do we do now?
嗯 现在我真的要开始工作了
Well, now I actually have to get to work.
"很有可能"
"Most likely."
- 好 我就在外面   - 好
- Okay, I'm gonna be out there.     - Okay.
- 好啦 再见   - 再见
- All right. Bye-bye.     - Bye-bye.
什么事？
Yes?
你在做什么？
What you doing?
好 窗户很干净 蜡烛都点了
Okay, windows are clean, candles are lit.
皮带太紧 要换皮带
Ooh, belt's too tight. Gotta change the belt.
鱼翻面了吗？没有 因为我做的是千层面
Did I turn the fish? Nope, because I made lasagna.
- 我是不是完全失控了？ - 一点点
- Am I out of control?     - Just a touch.
摩妮卡 我不懂
Mon, I don't understand.
你跟这个男的从… 期中考吧 就开始约会了
I mean, you've been dating this guy since, like, his midterms.
你为什么突然…？
I mean, why all of a sudden are you so?
哦
Oh.
什么？
What?
是不是就在今夜？
Could tonight be the night?
不知道
I don't know.
他是个很好的人 我喜欢跟他在一起 但是你也知道…
Look, he's a great guy, and I love being with him, but, you know...
事情该发生的时候就会发生
...things happen when they happen.
计划不了的
You don't plan these things.
- 你刮过腿毛了吗？ - 刮过了
- Oh. So did you shave your legs?     - Yeah.
唔…
Uh-huh.
能不能不要再钻牛角尖了 罗斯？那只是一个梦
Would you let it go, Ross? It was just a dream.
那不表示…
It doesn't mean...
来了 天啊 要生了 要生宝宝了
Oh, oh, oh. Oh, this is it. Oh, my God. It's baby time. Baby time.
别紧张 别紧张 不要紧张 轻松一点
All right, relax, relax, just relax, just relax. Be cool.
喂 哔哔机刚刚响
Yeah, hi, I was just beeped.
这里没有安德烈 今天已经第三次了
No, Andre is not here. Third time today.
对 我很确定
Yes, I am sure.
不 先生 我不提供那样的服务
Heh. No, sir, I do not perform those kind of services.
服务？哦 服务
Services? Oh, services.
对 您要打的是55-JUMBO
Yeah, you want 55-JUMBO.
对
Yeah.
没错
That's right.
没错 先生 有"U"的那个"JUMBO"
That's right. "JUMBO" with a U, sir.
您要的不是我
Heh. No, you don't want me.
以他的电话号码来判断 我会让您很失望
Judging by his number, I'd be a huge disappointment.
对 好的 再见
Yeah. Alrighty, bye-bye.
- 嘿 第一天上班的感觉怎样？ - 嘿
- Hey, hey. How was the first day?     - Hey. Oh.
很棒 大家都对我很好
Excellent. Everyone was so, so nice.
看吧？认识一个能穿我鞋子的人是有好处的
See? It pays to know the man who wears my shoes.
- 就是我啦   - 啊
- Me.     - Ah.
- 我没跟人说我本来就认识你   - 为什么？
- I didn't tell anybody that I knew you.     - Why not?
因为 嗯…
Well, because, you know.
他们不喜欢你
They don't like you.
- 什么？ - 你都不知道吗？
- What?     - I thought you knew that.
不…
Nah-uh.
- 谁不喜欢我？ - 大家
- Who doesn't like me?     - Everyone.
除了…
Except for, um...
不 大家都不喜欢
No. Everyone.
- 你在说什么？ - 不要难过
- What are you talking about?     - Don't feel bad.
他们以前其实很喜欢你
You know, they used to like you a lot.
但是你升官了 现在你变成老板
But then you got promoted, and now you're all, like, Mr. Boss-Man.
他们叫你宾先生 宾先生 宾老板
You know, Mr. Bing. Mr. Bing. Boss-Man Bing.
- 真不敢相信   - 他们还模仿你
- I can't believe it.     - Yeah, yeah. They even do you.
- 模仿我？ - 对啊
- They do me?     - Yeah.
就像这样…
You know, like, um, okay:
"那份报告可以再拖一点"
"Could that report be any later?"
我说话才不是那样
I don't sound like that.
- 钱德   - 就是那样
- Oh, oh. Chandler.     - Oh. Yeah, you do.
"群山在乐声中充满了…"
"The hills are alive with the sound...
"生气"
...of music."
"我的司康松糕 "
"My scone!"
少来 我说话不是那样子 那不是真的
Okay, I don't sound like that. That is so not true.
那不是… 那不是… 那…
That is so not... That is so not... That...
你们闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
不会吧
Ha, ha. You did not.
真的 一直到我9岁…
I am telling you, up until I was 9...
我都认为枪下就是人犯罪的地方
...I thought gunpoint was an actual place where crimes happened.
- 怎么可能？ - 你想想看 新闻不是一直在播
- Ha, ha. How is that possible?     - Think about it. It's always on the news.
"一名男子被架在枪下"
"A man is being held up at Gunpoint."
"观光客枪下惊魂"
"Tourists are being terrorized at Gunpoint."
我一直很疑惑 "为什么大家还是继续去那里？"
And I just kept thinking, "Why do people continue to go there?"
噢
Oh, ah.
- 我得走了   - 好吧
- I should go.     - Okay.
好
Okay.
- 除非…   - 什么？
- Unless...     - What?
你想在这里过夜
Uh, unless you wanna stay over.
我得在这里过夜 所以…
I mean, I'm going to. So...
好啊 我很愿意
Yeah, I'd really like that.
在真正开始过夜之前…
Uh, before we get into any staying-over stuff...
有些事要先让你知道
...there's something you should know.
好 是类似"我明天早上有一堂很早的课"的事…
Okay. Is this like "I have an early class tomorrow"...
还是"我已经跟一头山羊结婚了"？
...or "I'm secretly married to a goat"?
介于两者之间
Well, it's somewhere in between.
严格来说 我不算是…
You see, in a strictly technical sense, of course, I'm not, uh...
我是说 我从来没有…
Well, I mean, I haven't ever, um...
- 伊森？ - 什么事？
- Ethan?     - Yeah?
你是处男吗？
Are you a virgin?
如果这是你们这些孩子现代的说法…
Well, if that's what you kids are calling it these days...
那 对 我算是
...then yes, I am.
我一直在等待对的人出现
I, uh... I've kind of been waiting for the right person.
- 真的吗？ - 真的
- Really?     - Yeah.
你知道我是指你吧？
You do know I was talking about you, right?
哇
Wow.
你一直哇哇哇
You keep saying that.
这在书上看过 电影上也有
You know, you read about it. You see it in the movies.
就算在家里自己练习过 但是 天啊…
Even when you practice it at home, man, oh, man...
感觉完全不同
...it is nothing like that.
哦
Oh.
等一下 听着
Listen, listen.
你告诉一件 对你来说很难启齿的事
Um, you told me something that was really difficult for you.
我想 既然你可以对我说实话 我也可以对你说实话
And, um, well, I figure if you can be honest, then I can too.
- 天啊 不要告诉我我做错了   - 不是
- Oh, God, don't tell me I did it wrong.     - No.
- 不是 不是…   - 哦
- No, no, no.     - Oh.
- 完全正确   - 噢…
- Nothing wrong about that.     - Oh. Ha, ha.
好 是这样的
Um, okay. Here goes.
我不是22岁
I'm not 22.
我25…
I'm 25.
又13个月
And 13 months.
唔
Huh.
但是我想 这不应该有什么影响吧
But I figure, you know, that shouldn't change anything.
我们的年龄不是什么问题吧 对不对？
I mean, what the hell does it matter how old we are?
嗯…
Listen, um...
既然我们开始说实话了…
...as long as we're telling stuff, uh...
我还有一件事要告诉你
...I have another one for you.
我比当初说的要小一点
I'm a little younger than I said.
你不是在念最后一年了吗？
You're not a senior?
我是最后一年…
Oh, I'm a senior.
高中最后一年
In high school.
好吧
Okay.
我们做的事大错特错
What we did was wrong.
天啊 刚刚跟我上床的人 美国两百周年国庆时还不存在
Oh, God. I just had sex with someone who wasn't alive during the bicentennial.
我刚破处
I just had sex.
伊森 专心一点 你怎么不早点说？
Ethan, focus. How could you not tell me?
- 你也没告诉我你多大   - 那不一样
- You never told me how old you were.     - That's different.
我的谎话不会让我在48州都成为通缉犯
My lie didn't make one of us a felon in 48 states.
- 你有没有在用大脑？ - 我没在用大脑 我忙着…
- What were you thinking?     - I wasn't thinking. I was busy falling...
- 不要说出来   - 爱上你
- Don't say it.       - ...in love with you.
真的吗？
Really?
对不起
Sorry.
不要再爱我了
Well, fall out of it.
你根本不该在这里 明天还要上学
You know, you shouldn't even be here. It's a school night.
天啊 天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
我和那些专找乳臭未干的小子的女人没两样
I'm like those women that you see with shiny guys named Chad.
我是琼•考琳斯
I'm Joan Collins.
谁啊？
Who?
好吧 安德烈45分钟后就会回来
Okay, Andre should be there in about 45 minutes.
好的 再见
Alrighty. Bye-bye.
这样比较干脆
Ahem. It's just easier that way.
好啦 上次做的梦 你就肯说
Oh, come on. You told me about the last dream.
不要 不告诉你
No. Forget it.
为什么？我是不是做了什么特别销魂蚀骨的事？
Well, why not? Was I doing something particularly saucy?
好啦 好啦
All right, fine. Um...
当时不只有你
Well, you were not the only one there.
乔伊也在
Joey was there too.
好
All right.
还有…
Was there, uh, heh...
别人吗？
...anybody else there?
- 没有   - 你确定？
- No.     - You sure?
没有人在发薄荷糖之类的吗？
Nobody, uh, handing out mints or anything?
没有 就我们三个
No, it was just the three of us.
噢
Oh.
那么 是你先跟钱德 然后再你和我…
So tell me, was it like you and Chandler and then you and me...
还是你 我和钱德都在一起？
...or you and me and Chandler?
- 你知道吗？ - 什么？
- You know what?     - What?
有时候…
There were times...
根本没有我
...when it wasn't even me.
好甜蜜哦 你们两个
That is so sweet, you guys.
嘿 摩妮卡
Hey, Mon. Mon.
摩妮卡 伊森又打电话来了
Mon, Ethan called again.
摩妮卡？
Mon?
摩妮卡
Mon!
- 干嘛？ - 伊森又打电话来了
- What?     - Ethan called again.
哦
Oh.
- 你不跟他交往啦？ - 不了
- You're not seeing him anymore?     - No.
有时候 两个人就是没办法在一起
You know, sometimes just things don't work out.
这个跟他连络簿上要有家长签名才能不去上体育课有关吗？
And this has nothing to do with the fact that he needs a note to get out of gym?
我没说… 我什么都没说 我发誓
I didn't say any... I did not say anything, I swear.
他跑来看你
He stopped by.
改天你跟他说话的时候…
Next time you talk to him...
能不能问他哪个金刚战士威力最强大？
...could you ask him which one the strongest Power Ranger is?
哈哈 我的人生真是好笑 大家可以闭嘴了吗？
Oh, my life is just so amusing. Heh, heh. Can we drop it now?
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
金刚合体
It's morphing time.
- 剑龙   - 暴龙
- Stegosaurus!     - Tyrannosaurus!
我要走了
Ooh. Oh, I gotta go.
头晕
Whoa. Ooh, head rush. Oh.
再来一次 我就得出发了
One more and then I have to go.
酷
Cool. Ha, ha.
你要去哪里？
Where you going?
有同事要开生日派对
Oh, I got a birthday party with some work people.
同事？
Work people?
- 都没人告诉我   - 对啊 我知道
- Nobody told me.     - No, I know.
这个跟他们不喜欢你有很大的关系
That's part of the whole, you know, them-not-liking-you extravaganza.
我不懂 这些人一个月前都还是我的朋友
Know what? I don't get this. A month ago, these people were my friends.
现在我换了位置 不表示我的脑袋也换了
Just because I'm in charge, doesn't mean I'm a different person.
那你应该一起来 跟大家聊聊
Well, then you should come tonight, just hang out with them.
让他们看看你还是跟以前一样好玩好相处
Let them see what a great guy you still are.
- 你觉得我应该去吗？ - 对啊 真的
- You think I should?     - I really do, yeah.
- 好 好吧   - 好
- Okay. Okay.     - Okay.
但是 我们能不能不要一起出现？
Oh, but, um, could we not go together?
我不想当那个邀上司一起来的怪胎
I don't wanna be the geek who invited the boss, you know?
昨晚真是好玩
I think last night was great.
还唱卡啦OK？翠西跟我合唱《黑檀木与白象牙》？
You know, the karaoke thing? Tracy and I doing "Ebony and lvory"?
- 嗯…   - 哈
- Mm-hm.     - Ha, ha.
你很受欢迎 但是他们私底下还是会笑你
You were great. But they still made fun of you.
- 什么？ - 现在你成了关心下属先生
- What?     - Now you're more like Mr. Caring-Boss.
"我们可以同乐" 老板
Mr. "I'm-One-of-You"-Boss.
"我想跟你们一起混"的宾老板
Mr. "I-Wanna-Be-Your-Buddy"- Boss-Man-Bing.
这我就搞不清楚了
Then I don't get it.
你知道吗 钱德？我想你得面对现实
Well, you know what, Chandler? I think you just gotta face it.
你现在是那个有大办公室的人了
You're, like, the guy in the big office, you know?
你是那个操纵他们生死大权的的人了
You're the one that hires them and fires them.
- 他们还是觉得你是个好上司   - 真的吗？
- They still say you're a great boss.     - They do?
嗯
Uh-huh.
但是他们已经不是你的朋友了
But they're not your friends anymore.
- 但是我只想要…   - 但是你不行
- But I just want to...     - No, but you can't.
- 但是我只想要…   - 啊哈
- But I just want...     - Ah-ah.
中央咖啡馆
你不…？
Aren't you gonna...?
卡萝跟我约好了
Oh, Carol and I have a new system.
如果她打来 留下"911"就表示她要生了
If she punches in "911," it means she's having a baby.
- 其他的我都不管了   - 那安德烈怎么办？
- Otherwise, I just ignore it.     - What about Andre?
今天早上他接到 我觉得好像是我们表哥纳森的电话
This morning he got a call from what I think was our cousin Nathan.
说真的 我不想知道那么多
And frankly, it was a little more than I needed to know.
嘿
Hey.
我本来想抢先讲的
That was gonna be my opener.
嘿 你们看过厕所里面新的干手机吗？
Hey, did you guys check out those new hand dryers in the bathroom?
- 我以为那只是传闻   - 真的有
- I thought that was just a rumor.     - True story.
有件事我得告诉你
All right, look, I gotta tell you something.
我不是17岁
I'm not 17.
我说我17岁 这样才会让你感觉我可爱又脆弱
I only said that so you'd think I was cute and vulnerable.
我已经30了
I'm actually 30.
我有老婆 有工作 是你选区的国会议员
I have a wife. I have a job. I'm your congressman.
摩妮卡 这太离谱了 我们在一起很快乐
Monica, this is ridiculous. We are great together.
我们很有话聊 能逗对方笑 性生活 天啊 太美满了
We can talk, we make each other laugh. And the sex. Oh, man.
好 我是没得比较 但是我觉得很棒
Okay, I have no frame of reference, but I thought that was great.
- 是很棒   - 那么问题在哪里？
- It was.     - Then what's the problem?
伊森 这让人…
Ethan, it's, um...
太肉麻了
It's icky.
肉麻？
Icky?
就因为你觉得肉麻 就要放弃这段感情？
You're actually gonna throw this away because it's icky?
真的 我也很难受
Look, this isn't easy for me either.
我也希望情况不是这样
I wish things were different.
要是你大几岁 还是我小几岁…
If you were a few years older or I was a few years younger...
或是我们活在《圣经》时代…
...or we lived in biblical times...
- 我就可以…   - 不要说出来
- ...I could really...     - No, don't say it.
爱你
Love you.
- 你们手干了吗？ - 还是湿湿的
- Are your hands still wet?     - They're moist.
- 对啊   - 我们再去烘一下
- Yeah, right? Ahem.     - Let's dry them again.
还有 "这玛格莉特调酒 可以再烈一点"
Or, like, "Could these margaritas be any stronger?"
- 嘿 钱德   - 你好 宾先生
- Hey, Chandler.     - Hello, Mr. Bing.
你模仿史蒂夫•汪德真是惟妙惟肖
Loved your Stevie Wonder last night.
谢谢 每周报告我需要在…
Thanks. Listen, about the weekly numbers, I'm gonna need them on my desk...
9点前看到
...by 9:00.
- 当然   - 没问题
- Sure.     - No problem.
让他们忙一点是有必要的 你知道吧？
You have to give them something, you know?
好 那是葛斯顿 山多斯 那个有小胡子的是谁？
Okay, that was Gerston, Santos, and who's the guy with the mustache?
- 彼崔   - 彼崔 对 对 好
- Petrie.     - Petrie. Right, right, okay.
有人这个周末…
Well, some people are gonna be working...
要赶工了
...this weekend.
好舒服哦
Oh, that's nice.
罗斯
Ross.
- 罗斯？ - 我在这里
- Ross?     - I'm here.
你在这里？
You are?
嗯…
Uh... Ahem.
我们刚刚正在…
We were just...
- 哇   - 怎么了？
- Wow.     - What?
太好了 现在宝宝要出生了
Heh. Great. Now I'm having a baby.
- 什么？ - 噢
- What?     - Oh!
- 宝宝要… 宝宝要出生了   - 噢…
- No. I'm having... I'm having a baby!     - Oh. Oh!
- 天啊   - 宝宝要…
- Oh, my God.     - I'm having a...!
- 电话 电话   - 电话 电话不在我这边
- The phone, the phone!     - The phone. I don't have the phone. Aah!
- 罗斯？ - 好痛
- Ross?     - I'm hurt.
摩妮卡 快点 动作快 有人要生了
Monica, let's go. Come on, now, people. Woman in labor.
- 嘿 罗斯 你看我会这样   - 车上再说 可以吗？
- Hey, Ross, look what I got going here.     - Yeah, save it for the cab, okay?
你在干什么？我们是要去医院
What are you doing? We're going to a hospital.
怎么？我不能打扮一下吗？那边也许有很多医生
What, so I can't look nice? There might be doctors there.
- 乔伊 不要再翻冰箱了   - 好啦 好啦
- Joey, get out of the fridge.     - All right, all right.
- 那是什么？ - 车上吃的
- What is that?     - For the ride.
- 是啦 在计程车上…   - 待会儿再说
- Yeah, like in a cab you...     - Save it.
- 这样很讨厌   - 摩妮卡 快点 我们要走了
- Okay, hating this.     - Monica, come on, now. Let's go.
宝宝快出来了 天啊
Baby coming. God.
真不敢相信我要当姑姑了
I can't believe it. I'm gonna be an aunt.
- 那真是…   - 我快要有侄儿了
- Oh, that's...     - I'm gonna have a nephew.
真感人 快滚
Oh, that's nice. Get out.
- 快点   - 我们快走 快点
- Come on.     - Let's go, come on.
好啦 好啦
Okay. Okay.
好啦 好啦 在走了 在走了
All right, all right, I'm going, I'm going.
- 冷静   - 罗斯 冷静 乖
- Here we go. Here we go.     - Rossy. Rossy.